Menu

Menu

* Product
    * [Hosting
        
        Podcast hosting and distribution](https://castos.com/podcast-hosting-platform)
    * [Private Podcasting
        
        Secure access to private subscribers](https://castos.com/private-podcasting-solutions/)
    * [Mobile App
        
        Concierge private podcasting experience](https://castos.com/mobile-app/)
    * [Internal Company Podcasts
        
        Stay connected with your team through podcasting](https://castos.com/internal-company-podcast/)
    * [WordPress
        
        Seriously Simple Podcasting Plugin](https://castos.com/seriously-simple-podcasting/)
    * [Enterprise Solutions
        
        White glove assistance for your podcasts](https://castos.com/enterprise-podcast-platform/)
* Features
    * [Custom Website
        
        Get a free website as unique as your podcast](https://castos.com/customizable-podcast-website/)
    * [Automatic Podcast Transcriptions
        
        Spend time creating your podcast not transcribing it](https://castos.com/transcription/)
    * [Dynamic Ads
        
        Automatically place highly relevant ads in all your episodes](https://castos.com/advertising)
    * [Get Paid To Podcast
        
        Accept payments directly from your listeners](https://castos.com/commerce)
    * [YouTube Republishing
        
        Reach your audience on the largest search engine](https://castos.com/youtube-republishing/)
    * [Podcast Analytics
        
        Grow your Audience with the right analytics](https://castos.com/podcast-analytics/)
* Services
    * [Award Winning Podcast Editing Service
        
        Done For You Production Of Every Episode](https://castos.com/productions/)
    * [Podcast Launch Service
        
        Launch Your Podcast The Right Way](https://castos.com/services/podcast-launch-service)
    * [Podcast Gallery
        
        Check Out A Few Of The Shows We Work With](https://castos.com/services/our-work/)
* Resources

Privacy
=======

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

 When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey or enter information on our site.

When you visit or log in to our website, cookies and similar technologies may be used by our online data partners or vendors to associate these activities with other personal information they or others have about you, including by association with your email or home address. We may then send communications and marketing to these email addresses.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Castos collects aggregated, anonymous statistics in order to provide listener data for our customers. We log information about each download of an episode including data like IP addresses and user-agents. We then display this information on a podcast episode level to our customers in the form of Castos Analytics.

IP addresses are all hashed as they are stored in our system so none of this data is personally identifiable.  Castos never stores directly the IP address of podcast listeners, but rather a hashed version of IP addresses which is generalized to a State or City level.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

**•** To improve our website in order to better serve you.

**•** To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

**•** To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

**How do we protect visitor information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

#### Security

We strive to use a variety of the best security measures to help keep your information secure. For example, all communication with this website requires HTTPS. Passwords are not stored directly, they are hashed securely using advanced, well-tested methods.

**Credit Cards**

All credit card information is handled securely by our credit card processor, [Stripe](https://stripe.com/). Castos _does not_ collect, store, or process your credit card information directly.

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

A ‘cookie’ is a small text file sent from a website and stored on the user’s computer by the user’s web browser. Upon visiting a site that uses cookies, a cookie is downloaded onto your computer or mobile device.  The next time you visit that site, your device will remember useful information such as preferences, visited pages or logging in options.

Cookies are widely used to add functionality to websites, or to ensure they work more efficiently. Our site relies on cookies to optimise the user experience and ensure the sites services function properly.

To optimize the user experience for our customers we use cookies from Google Analytics and Facebook on our website.

Our Website uses cookies and other tracking and monitoring software to: distinguish our users from one another; collect standard Internet log information; and to collect visitor behavior information. The information is used to track user interactions with the Website and allows us to provide you with a good experience when you access the Website, helps us to improve our Website, and allows us to compile statistical reports on Website visitors and Website activity.

Most web browsers allow some control to restrict or block cookies through the browser settings, however if you disable cookies you may find this affects your ability to use certain parts of our website or services. For more information about cookies please visit https://www.aboutcookies.org.

**Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.

**Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**YouTube**

Customers utilizing our Republishing feature to distribute their podcast content in video form to YouTube will be subject to [Google’s Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy) and YouTube’s [Terms of Service](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms). Castos’ YouTube Republishing feature utilizes the YouTube API to distribute podcast episodes directly to Customers’ YouTube channels.

**We have implemented the following:**

**•** Demographics and Interests Reporting

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the Facebook cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiativeoptoutpage or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?**

It’s also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking

**Your Data Rights**

You may exercise your rights to access, correct, erase, object to processing, and request data portability where applicable in the following ways:

* Changing your profile information by accessing the Settings page of the Castos dashboard.
* You may request that your account be deleted entirely by submitting a request to us via email at [\[email protected\]](https://castos.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) – this request will be processed within 14 days and you will be notified when your data has been removed from our systems.

#### Retention

Castos retains personal information you provide to create your account for as long as you maintain an account with us. Personal information used to provide the services to you will be kept long enough to provide you with the service, including in archives and logs used to maintain and develop the service. We may retain some usage statistics (including IP addresses) for as long as we have a business purpose in order to improve Castos’ services, but these statistics are no longer linked to a deleted account.

**Information for European Union Customers**

By using Castos and providing your information, you authorize us to collect, use, and store your information outside of the European Union.

#### International Transfers of Information

Information may be processed, stored, and used outside of the country in which you are located. Data privacy laws vary across jurisdictions, and different laws may be applicable to your data depending on where it is processed, stored, or used.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

[\[email protected\]](https://castos.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Castos, Inc  
1209 North Orange Street  
Wilmington, DE 19801  
United States

Last updated: April 28, 2023

**Castos** runs **entirely** on **renewable energy**.

Switching
---------

Resources
---------

Company
-------

* Castos, Inc  
    1209 North Orange St.  
    Wilmington, DE 19801

Product
-------

© 2024, Castos Inc. All Rights Reserved.
